facebd.com 2012-09-22

# FaceBD.com Privacy Policy

FACEBD Corp ("FACEBD") recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information collected about its users. FACEBD adopted this Privacy Policy to inform FaceBD.com users how it does collect, store, and use personal information. "Personal information" includes, but is not limited to, usage data, along with the name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information of FaceBD.com users. Therefore, FACEBD does not sell or otherwise disclose any individually identifiable personal information about any user without an express and informed consent of such user. Nor does FACEBD include in FaceBD.com any functionality for performing "reverse searches" to identify FaceBD.com users from their e-mail addresses. However, FACEBD reserves the right to analyze and utilize user data in order to more effectively optimize the user experience and to present certain opportunities to users for their benefit. FACEBD also reserves the right to share with its partners and third parties some personal information on the aggregate basis only and provided that such use of personal information does not violate any expectations of privacy of or agreement with any FaceBD.com user. FACEBD's intent is to balance its legitimate business interests in collecting and using personal information against the reasonable expectations of privacy of its users.

## Information Collection and Use

### Information Collection

FACEBD is the sole owner of the information collected on FaceBD.com. FACEBD collects information from our users at following points on our Web site. 

**Registration**  
In order to customize FaceBD site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as email address). We do not collect user's name and address. We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is also required for the user to provide demographic information (such as age group, gender, city and country), and unique identifiers (such as, username and password).

### Information Use

FACEBD uses personal information for: developing enhancements to FaceBD.com; marketing and promotional purposes; and evaluating FaceBD.com usage by analyzing and otherwise using personal information and related data in the aggregate, but not with respect to any individual FaceBD.com user.In addition, FACEBD uses personal information to direct e-mail to FaceBD.com users who provide their e-mail address in connection with specific promotions, or to direct e-mail regarding FaceBD.com updates and service enhancements to users who opt in during the AllYouCanRed.com registration process.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We currently do not use cookies on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by FaceBD.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a tracking utility called Webtrends that uses log files to analyze user movement.

## Sharing

**Aggregate Information** (non-personally identifiable)  
FACEBD shares aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information:

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event FACEBD goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

## Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information.Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by offering an opt-out mechanism on the "My News" pages or contacting us at: **facebd.com[AT]gmail[DOT]com**.Users of FaceBD.com are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

## Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, FACEBD, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

##  Security

FACEBD takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected.   

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to: **facebd[AT]FACEBD[DOT]com**.

## Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as email or country), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at: **facebd[AT]FACEBD[DOT]com** .

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

## Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: **facebd.com[AT]gmail[DOT]com.**
